Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 6 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 7 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 8 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 9 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 10 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 11 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 12 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 13 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 14 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 15 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; 16 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 17 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 18 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 19 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 20 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 21 (Box 3)
  Notes: Compilation issue featuring Trevor Von Eeden, Jerome Moore and Ron Randall
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 22 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 23 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 24 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 25 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 26 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 27 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; 28 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1986; 29 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1986; 30 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1986; 31 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1986; 32 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1984; A1 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1985; A2 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: David Ross
- Batman/Hellboy/Starman, 1998; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: James Robinson
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Mignola
  Publisher: DC/Dark Horse
- Batman/Hellboy/Starman, 1998; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman/Superman/Wonder Woman: Trinity, 2003; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Matt Wagner
  Artist/Penciler: Dave Stewart
- Batman/Superman/Wonder Woman: Trinity, 2003; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Batgirl, 1997; TPB (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Matt Haley
- Batman: Batgirl, 1998; 1 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Jim Balent and Rick Bruchett
  Notes: Girlfrenzy crossover
- Batman: Black and White, 1996; 1 (Box 4)
  Notes: Four issue miniseries featuring multiple artists and writers
- Batman: Black and White, 1996; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: Black and White, 1996; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Black and White, 1996; 4 (Box 4)
- Batman: City of light, 2003; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Mark Paniccia
  Artist/Penciler: Alvard Lopez
  Notes: eight issue miniseries
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Jeph Loeb
  Artist/Penciler: Tim Sale
  Notes: fourteen issue miniseries sequel to Long Halloween
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 2 (Box 4)
  Notes: fourteen issue miniseries
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 4 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 5 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 6 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 7 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 8 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 9 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 10 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 11 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 1999; 12 (Box 4)
- Batman: Dark victory, 2000; 13 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 1 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 4 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 5 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 6 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 7 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1998; 8 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 9 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 10 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 11 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 12 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 13 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 14 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 15 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 16 (Box 4)
- Batman: Gotham Adventures, 1999; 17 (Box 4)
- Batman: Harley and Ivy, 2004; 1 (Box 4)
- Batman: Harley and Ivy, 2004; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: Harley and Ivy, 2004; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Harley Quinn, 1999 (Box 4)
- Batman: Hush, 2001; Vol. 1 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Jim Lee
  Notes: TPB, 2nd printing
- Batman: Hush, 2001; Vol. 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1989; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Dennis O'Neil
  Artist/Penciler: Edward Hannigan
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1993; 42 (Box 4)
  Author: John Francis Moore
  Artist/Penciler: P. Craig Russell
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1993; 43 (Box 4)
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1994; 64 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Chris Bachalo
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1995; 72 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: John Watkiss
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1995; 74 (Box 4)
  Author: Ted McKeever
  Artist/Penciler: Ted McKeever
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1995; 75 (Box 4)
- Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, 1995; 76 (Box 4)
  Author: Scott Hampton
  Artist/Penciler: Scott Hampton
- Batman: Man-Bat, 1995; 1 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: John Bolton
  Notes: three issue minseries
- Batman: Man-Bat, 1995; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: Man-Bat, 1995; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Mr. Freeze, 1997; tpb (Box 4)
- Batman: Poison Ivy, 1997; tpb (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Brian Apthorp
- Batman: Shadow of the Bat, 1993; 11 (Box 4)
  Author: Alan Grant
  Artist/Penciler: Vince Ciarrano
- Batman: Shadow of the Bat, 1993; 12 (Box 4)
- Batman: Shadow of the Bat, 1996; 56 (Box 4)
- Batman: Shadow of the Bat, 1996; 57 (Box 4)
- Batman: Sword of Azrael, 1992; 2 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Joe Quesada
- Batman: Sword of Azrael, 1992; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: Sword of Azrael, 1993; 4 (Box 4)
- Batman: the 10¢ adventure, 2001 (Box 4)
  Author: Greg Rucka
- Batman: The Doom that came to Gotham, 1999; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Mike Mignola
  Artist/Penciler: Troy Nixey
- Batman: The Doom that came to Gotham, 1999; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1996; 1 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1996; 2 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1996; 3 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 4 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 5 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 6 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 7 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 8 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 9 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 10 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 11 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 12 (Box 4)
- Batman: The Long Halloween, 1997; 13 (Box 4)
- Batman:Nosferatu, 1998 (Box 4)
  Author: Randy Lofficier
  Artist/Penciler: Jean-Marc Lofficier
- Battleaxes, 2000; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Jerry Laban
  Artist/Penciler: Alex Horley
  Notes: four issue miniseries
- Beast Boy, 2000; 1 (Box 4)
  Notes: four issue miniseries; Teen Titans spinoff
- Beast Boy, 2000; 2 (Box 4)
- Beast Boy, 2000; 3 (Box 4)
- Beast Boy, 2000; 4 (Box 4)
- Beast that Ate Morioka, The, 2004 (Box 4)
- Beauty and the Beast, 1984; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Ann Nocenti
  Artist/Penciler: Don Perlin
  Notes: four issue miniseries; X-men spinoff
- Beauty and the Beast, 1984; 2 (Box 4)
- Beauty and the Beast, 1984; 3 (Box 4)
- Beauty and the Beast, 1984; 4 (Box 4)
- Beware the Creeper, 2003; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Jason Hall
  Artist/Penciler: Cliff Chiang
- Beware the Creeper, 2003; 2 (Box 4)
- Beware the Creeper, 2003; 3 (Box 4)
- Big Bang Comics, 1995; 0 (Box 4)
  Notes: five issue miniseries; various artists
- Big Bang Comics, 1996; 1 (Box 4)
- Big Bang Comics, 1996; 2 (Box 4)
- Big Bang Comics, 1996; 3 (Box 4)
- Big Bang Comics, 1996; 4 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1993; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Dick Foreman
  Notes: Ongoing series
- Black Orchid, 1993; 2 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1993; 3 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1993; 4 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 5 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 6 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 7 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Rebecca Guay
- Black Orchid, 1994; 8 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 9 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 10 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 11 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 12 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 13 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 14 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 15 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1994; 16 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; 17 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; 18 (Box 4)
  Artist/Penciler: Jamie Tolagson
- Black Orchid, 1995; 19 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; 20 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; 21 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; 22 (Box 4)
- Black Orchid, 1995; Ann. 1 (Box 4)
- Blanche goes to Hollywood, 1993 (Box 4)
  Author: Rick Geary
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Geary
- Blanche goes to New York, 1993; — (Box 4)
- Blood Syndicate, 1993; 1 (Box 4)
  Publisher: DC/Icon
- Blood Syndicate, 1994; 27 (Box 4)
  Author: Ivan Velez, Jr.
  Artist/Penciler: Chriscross
- Blood: a tale, 1996; 1 (Box 4)
  Author: Jim DeMatteis
  Artist/Penciler: Kent Williams
  Notes: four part miniseries
- Blood: a tale, 1996; 2 (Box 4)
- Blood: a tale, 1996; 3 (Box 4)
- Blood: a tale, 1996; 4 (Box 4)
- Bloodhound, 2004; 5 (Box 4)
  Author: Dan Jolley
  Artist/Penciler: Leonard Kirk
  Notes: continues story from firestorm (2d series) #7
- Bone, 1992; 1 (Box 5)
  Author: Jeff Smith
  Artist/Penciler: Jeff Smith
  Publisher: Cartoon Books
  Notes: signed by Jeff Smith, reprint
- Bone, 1996; 1 (Box 5)
  Notes: Reprint, reprint
- Bone, 1993; 2 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 3 (Box 5)
  Notes: signed by Jeff Smith
- Bone, 1993; 4 (Box 5)
  Notes: 2nd printing
- Bone, 1993; 5 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 6 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 7 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 8 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 9 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 10 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1993; 11 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1994; 12 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1994; 13 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1994; 14 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1994; 15 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1994; 16 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1995; 17 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1995; 18 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1995; 19 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1995; 20 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1995; 21 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1996; 22 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1996; 23 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1996; 24 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1996; 25 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1996; 26 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1997; 27 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1997; 28 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1997; 29 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1998; 30 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1998; 31 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1998; 32 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1998; 34 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1999; 35 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1999; 36 (Box 5)
- Bone, 1999; 37 (Box 5)
  Notes: Variant cover (no logo)
- Bone, 2000; 38 (Box 5)
  Notes: Charles Vess cover art
- Bone, 2000; 39 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2001; 40 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2001; 41 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2001; 42 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2001; 43 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2001; 44 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 45 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 46 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 47 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 48 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 49 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2002; 50 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2003; 51 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2003; 52 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2004; 53 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2004; 54 (Box 5)
- Bone, 2004; 55 (Box 5)
- Bone Holiday Special, 1993 (Box 5)
  Notes: Hero premiere edition
- Book of Ballads and Sagas, 1995; 1 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Charles Vess
  Publisher: Green Man Press
  Notes: four issue biannual miniseries; various writers
- Book of Ballads and Sagas, 1995; 2 (Box 5)
- Book of Ballads and Sagas, 1996; 3 (Box 5)
- Book of Ballads and Sagas, 1996; 4 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie, 1997; 1 (Box 5)
  Author: Bronwyn Carlton
- Books of Faerie, 1997; 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie, 1997; 3 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Auberon's tale, 1998; 1 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Auberon's tale, 1998; 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Auberon's tale, 1998; 3 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Molly's story, 1999; 1 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Hermann Mejia
- Books of Faerie: Molly's story, 1999; 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Molly's story, 1999; 3 (Box 5)
- Books of Faerie: Molly's story, 1999; 4 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.1), 1990; 1 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.1), 1990; 1 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.1), 1990; 1 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.1), 1991; 1 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Johnson
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 1 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Gary Amaro
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 3 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 4 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 5 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Peter Snejbjerg
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 6 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 7 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1994; 8 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 9 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 10 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 11 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 12 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 13 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 14 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 15 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 16 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 17 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 18 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 19 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1995; 20 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 21 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: John Ridgway
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 22 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 23 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 24 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 25 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 26 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 27 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 28 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 29 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1996; 30 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 31 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 32 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 33 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 34 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 35 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 36 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 37 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 38 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 39 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 40 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 41 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 42 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; 43 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 44 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 45 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 46 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 47 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 48 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 49 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 50 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 51 (Box 5)
  Author: Peter Gross
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 52 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 53 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 54 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; 55 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Peter Gross and Linda Medley
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 56 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 57 (Box 5)
  Notes: books of faerie cross-over
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 58 (Box 5)
  Author: Peter Gross and Bronwyn Carlton
  Artist/Penciler: Hermann Mejia and Temujin
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 59 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 60 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 61 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 62 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 63 (Box 5)
  Author: Peter Hogan
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 64 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 65 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 66 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; 67 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 68 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 69 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Vince Locke
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 70 (Box 5)
  Artist/Penciler: Ryan Kelley
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 71 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 72 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 73 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 74 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 2000; 75 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1997; Ann. 1 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1998; Ann. 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Magic (v.2), 1999; Ann. 3 (Box 5)
  Notes: Compilation issue
- Books of Magick: Life During Wartime, 2004; 1 (Box 5)
  Author: Si Spencer
  Artist/Penciler: Dean Ormston
- Books of Magick: Life During Wartime, 2004; 2 (Box 5)
- Books of Magick: Life During Wartime, 2004; 3 (Box 5)
- Books of Magick: Life During Wartime, 2004; 4 (Box 5)
- Books of Magick: Life During Wartime, 2005; 5 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1996; 1 (Box 5)
  Author: Alex Robinson
  Artist/Penciler: Alex Robinson
  Publisher: Antarctic
- Box Office Poison, 1996; 2 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 3 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 4 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 5 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 6 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 7 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1997; 8 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1998; 9 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1998; 10 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1998; 11 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1998; 12 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1999; 13 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1999; 14 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1999; 15 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 1999; 16 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 2000; 17 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 2000; 18 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 2000; 19 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 2000; 20 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison, 2000; 21 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison Kolor Karnival, 1999; 1 (Box 5)
- Box Office Poison Super Special, 1997; 0 (Box 5)
- BPRD: Dark waters, 2003 (Box 6)
  Author: Brian Augustyn
  Artist/Penciler: Guy Davis
  Notes: Hell Boy spinoff
- BPRD: Hollow Earth, 2002; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Mike Mignola, Christopher Golden, Tom Sniegoski
  Artist/Penciler: Ryan Sook
- BPRD: Hollow Earth, 2002; 2 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Hollow Earth, 2002; 3 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Night train, 2003 (Box 6)
  Author: Geoff Johns
  Artist/Penciler: Scott Kolins
- BPRD: Plague of frogs, 2003; 1 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Plague of frogs, 2003; 2 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Plague of frogs, 2003; 3 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Plague of frogs, 2003; 4 (Box 6)
- BPRD: Plague of frogs, 2003; 5 (Box 6)
- BPRD: The dead, 2004; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Mike Mignola, John Arcudi
- BPRD: The dead, 2004; 2 (Box 6)
- BPRD: The dead, 2004; 3 (Box 6)
- BPRD: The dead, 2004; 4 (Box 6)
- BPRD: The soul of venice, 2003 (Box 6)
  Author: Miles Gunter
  Artist/Penciler: Michael Avon Oeming
- BPRD: There's something under my bed, 2003 (Box 6)
  Author: Joe Harris
  Artist/Penciler: Adam Pollina
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Andi Watson
  Artist/Penciler: Andi Watson
  Publisher: Oni
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 2 (Box 6)
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 3 (Box 6)
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 4 (Box 6)
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 5 (Box 6)
- Breakfast After Noon, 2000; 6 (Box 6)
- Captain America, 1969; 109 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Jack Kirby
- Cartoon Network, 1997; - (Box 6)
  Author: Michael Kraiger
  Artist/Penciler: Glenn Barr
  Notes: Cover title: "Holy Cow! A free Cartoon Network comic"
- Cartoon Network Presents, 1997; 4 (Box 6)
  Author: Genndy Tartakosvsky
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Rudish
- Castle Waiting, 2002; 14 (Box 6)
  Author: Linda Medley
  Artist/Penciler: Linda Medley
  Publisher: Fantagraphics
- Castle Waiting, 2002; 15 (Box 6)
- Castle Waiting, 2002; 16 (Box 6)
- Casual Heroes, 1995; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Kevin McCarthy
  Artist/Penciler: Kevin McCarthy
- Catwoman, 2002; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Ed Brubaker
  Artist/Penciler: Darwyn Cooke
- Catwoman, 2002; 2 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 3 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 4 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 5 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Brad Rader
- Catwoman, 2002; 6 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 7 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 8 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 9 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 10 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2002; 11 (Box 6)
  Author: Steven Grant
- Catwoman, 2002; 12 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Cameron Stewart
- Catwoman, 2003; 13 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 14 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 15 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 16 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 17 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Javier Pulido
- Catwoman, 2003; 18 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 19 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 20 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 21 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 22 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 23 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2003; 24 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 25 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 26 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Gulacy
- Catwoman, 2004; 27 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 28 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 29 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 30 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 31 (Box 6)
- Catwoman, 2004; 32 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Sean Phillips
- Catwoman, 2004; 33 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Diego Olmos
- Catwoman: When in Rome, 2004; 1 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Time Sale
  Notes: miniseries
- Catwoman: When in Rome, 2004; 2 (Box 6)
- Catwoman: When in Rome, 2004; 3 (Box 6)
- Catwoman: When in Rome, 2004; 4 (Box 6)
- Cavalcade of Boys, 2002 (Box 6)
  Author: Tim Fish
  Artist/Penciler: Jay Laird
  Publisher: Ten Minute Cartoons
- Charlemagne, 1993; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: D.G. Chichester
  Publisher: Defiant
  Notes: Free copies from focus group session.
- Charlemagne, 1993; 2 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Pat McGreal, David Rawson
  Artist/Penciler: Chas Truog
  Notes: ten issue miniseries
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 2 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 3 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 4 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 5 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1995; 6 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1996; 7 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1996; 8 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1996; 9 (Box 6)
- Chiaroscuro, 1996; 10 (Box 6)
- Children's Crusade, 1993; 1 (Box 6)
- Children's Crusade, 1994; 2 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Alisa Kwitney
- Chronos, 1998; 1 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Guinan
- Chronos, 1998; 2 (Box 6)
- Chronos, 1998; 3 (Box 6)
- Chronos, 1998; 4 (Box 6)
- Chronos, 1998; 5 (Box 6)
- Chronos, 1998; 6 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1994; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Alan Davis
- Clandestine, 1994; 2 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1994; 3 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 4 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 5 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 6 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 7 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 8 (Box 6)
- Clandestine, 1995; 9 (Box 6)
- Classics Illustrated: Through the looking glass, 1990; 3 (Box 6)
  Artist/Penciler: Kyle Baker
  Publisher: First
- Cloak and Dagger (v.1), 1983; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Bill Mantilo
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Leonardi
- Cloak and Dagger (v.1), 1983; 2 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.1), 1983; 3 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.1), 1983; 4 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.2), 1985; 1 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.2), 1985; 2 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.2), 1985; 3 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.2), 1985; 4 (Box 6)
- Cloak and Dagger (v.2), 1985; 6 (Box 6)
- Clowns, The (Box 6)
  Author: P. Craig Russell
  Artist/Penciler: Galen Showman
  Notes: Opera adaptation
- comico collection, 1987; — (Box 6)
  Publisher: Comico
  Notes: Limited ed. slipcase containing: Grendel: Devil's Vagary, Comico Attractions 8, Elementals 12, Grendel 4, Next Man 3, Jonny Quest 2, Robotech: The Macross Saga 13, Robotech Masters 9, Evangeline 2, Star Blazers 4, Robotech: The New Generation 3, Justice Machine 6, Comico subscription sheet
- Concrete: Eclectica, 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Paul Chadwick
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Chadwick
- Concrete: Eclectica, 1993; 2 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Fragile creature, 1991; 1 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Fragile creature, 1991; 2 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Fragile creature, 1991; 3 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Fragile creature, 1991; 4 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Killer smile, 1994; 1 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Killer smile, 1994; 2 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Killer smile, 1994; 3 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Killer smile, 1994; 4 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Strange armor, 1997; 1 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Strange armor, 1997; 2 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Strange armor, 1997; 3 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Strange armor, 1997; 4 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Strange armor, 1997; 5 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 1 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 2 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 3 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 4 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 5 (Box 6)
- Concrete: Think like a mountain, 1996; 6 (Box 6)
- Creature from the Black Lagoon, 1993 (Box 6)
  Author: Steve Moncuse
  Artist/Penciler: Art Adams
  Notes: Indicia title: Universal Monsters: Creature from the Black Lagoon
- Creeper, the, 1997; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Len Kaminski
  Artist/Penciler: Shawn Martinbrough
- Creeper, the, 2 (Box 6)
- Crimson Plague, 1997; 1 (Box 6)
  Publisher: Event
- Crimson Plague, 2000; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: George Perez
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 1 (Box 6)
  Author: Marv Wolfman
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 2 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 3 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 4 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 5 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 6 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 7 (Box 6)
- Crisis on Infinite Earths, 1985; 8 (Box 6)